[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Madagascar is the worlds largest producer and exporter of what product?", "correct_answer": "Vanilla", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugarcane", "Tapioca", "Rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Resurrected, The Bourne Supremacy and United 93 are probably the best known movies by this British-born director.", "correct_answer": "Paul Greengrass", "incorrect_answers": ["Sike Jonze", "Don Siegel", "Oscar Micheaux"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Cheech and Chongs neighbor from whom they steal marijuana in the movie Nice Dreams?", "correct_answer": "Weird Jimmy", "incorrect_answers": ["Fun Bobby", "Smokin Steve", "Crazy Dave"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is generally accepted that paper money was invented in this nation.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "The Netherlands", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest subspecies of ostrich on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Red-necked Ostrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Southern Ostrich", "Masai Ostrich", "Middle Eastern Ostrich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose was the proposal to use the 16th letter of the Greek alphabet, \u03c0, as a symbol for Archimedes constant, also known as Ludolphs number?", "correct_answer": "William Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Isaac Newton", "Leonhard Euler", "Archimedes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the director of the 2008 movie Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["James Cameron", "Tim Burton", "Mel Gibson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first actor to play Tarzan?", "correct_answer": "Elmo Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Weissmuller", "Mike Henry", "Ron Ely"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He invented the vulcanized rubber double-tube tire in 1845 and the glass fountain pen in 1849. He also came up with the technique of firing explosive charges using electricity.", "correct_answer": "Robert William Thomson", "incorrect_answers": ["Edouard Michelin", "B. F. Goodrich", "Edouard Goodyear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Chinese Crested dogs ears are not cropped.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country is not a member of the Adriatic Euroregion?", "correct_answer": "Serbia", "incorrect_answers": ["Montenegro", "Albania", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you bet on a number in roulette in a fancy casino in Monaco or in an average casino in the USA, your odds of winning are the same.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]